{
    "subject": "resource/Gabriella_Wilde",
    "predicate": "property/alternativeNames",
    "object": "Calthorpe, Gabriella; Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe, Gabriella Zanna Vanessa",
    "human_readable": "Gabriella Wilde has alternative names such as Calthorpe, Gabriella; Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe, Gabriella Zanna Vanessa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9714564681053162,
            "question": "What are some alternative names for Gabriella Wilde?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9617521166801453,
            "question": "Is 'Calthorpe' a name used by Gabriella Wilde?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914703905582428,
            "question": "Which names are associated with Gabriella Wilde?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8515464663505554,
            "question": "Can you provide different forms of Gabriella Wilde's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8215993046760559,
            "question": "What is Gabriella Wilde's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8151865005493164,
            "question": "Does Gabriella Wilde use multiple names professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.803272545337677,
            "question": "List all the names used by Gabriella Wilde."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8019383549690247,
            "question": "What are the different variations of Gabriella Wilde's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7995632886886597,
            "question": "Does Gabriella Wilde have any other names besides her birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059156656265259,
            "question": "What are some aliases used by Gabriella Wilde?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gabriella Wilde has alternative names such as Calthorpe, Gabriella; Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe, Gabriella Zanna Vanessa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4597_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Gabriella Wilde have any other names besides her birth name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4597_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the different variations of Gabriella Wilde's name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4597_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=List all the names used by Gabriella Wilde.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4597_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4597_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention various alternative names for Gabriella Wilde, including Calthorpe and Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Gabriella Wilde's full name and her alternative names, which include Calthorpe and Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe. Therefore, the statement that Gabriella Wilde has alternative names such as Calthorpe, Gabriella; Anstruther-Gough-Calthorpe, Gabriella Zanna Vanessa is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}